

PROFILE

I have always had a passion for serving, helping, and inspiring others, and it is a value that I have integrated and expanded upon in all my professional ventures. From working in a gym and grocery store to climbing 400ft telecom towers on top of mountain peaks to maintain the cell network, I certainly have a colorful and unique background! Currently, I am studying to develop software programs to positively impact users of various integrated technologies.

Evidenced by my work experience, I have a proven track record of excelling at my job, fast-tracking myself to promotions, and opening the doors to new opportunities for growth within a company.

CONTACT

PHONE: 610-297-5163

EMAIL:

Deleona144@gmail.com

ADDRESS:

1554 Montessori Terrace Charlottesville, VA 22911

HOBBIES

Parkour & Fitness All Things "TESLA" Border Collies Self-Improvement

ANTHONY DELEON

Software Student

EDUCATION

LEARNING ALLIANCE CORPORATION (LAC): (Tampa, FL)

October 2022 – November 2022

Completed the Rigorous 5-week program at LAC, coming out of the trade school with a multitude of industry recognized Certifications, a job lined up with **TTS**, and as an integral member of the winning team on the competitive final project.

PARKLAND HIGH SCHOOL: (Allentown, PA)

2015 – 2019, Graduated High School with High Honors and Exceptional Participation

WORK EXPERIENCE

TELECOMMUNICATIONS TECHNICAL SERVICES (TTS):

Tower Technician, Cable Installer

December 2022 - August 2024

Climbed Towers for the first year, earning the **TOP PERFORMER** award in 2023 for my contributions to the SSN Project. I was **Promoted** to a regional Field Engineer, crosstrained as a cable installer, and completed an apprenticeship program through LAC

GIG-JOBS: Delivery Driver on InstaCart, GoPuff, DoorDash, & UberEats
Consistent 5-Star Ratings and performance across all active delivery apps

WEGMANS: Helping Hands, Maintenance, Front End Cashier

January 2021 – July 2022

Assisted multiple departments, applying my previous talents across the Front End, Maintenance, and Store Operation Teams. I was Afforded the honor to join the Simplification Team, responsible for auditing departments for accountability of health, service, cleanliness, and organizational standards. Recognized as **Top Talent** through various **Promotion Opportunities** and employee appreciation programs.

PLANET FITNESS: Member Services Rep, Maintenance & Cleaning

February 2020 - February 2021

I was **Swiftly Promoted** into the maintenance/cleaning department in recognition of my **High Standards**, detail-oriented approach, problem solving capabilities, and desire to grow on the job.

ADDITIONAL CERTIFICATES

- CPR/First Aid
- Bloodborne Pathogens Certificate